<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: self | Sourdough Labs Research and Development Corp.]]></title>
  <link href="http://sourdoughlabs.com/blog/categories/self/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sourdoughlabs.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-23T07:05:21-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sourdoughlabs.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new look]]></title>
    <link href="http://sourdoughlabs.com/blog/2013/03/23/intro/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-23T06:09:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sourdoughlabs.com/blog/2013/03/23/intro</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Focusing on Credit Unions</h2>

<p>The reason for turing this site into pure blog from the services landing page that was here before is that I would like to move away from generic consulting/contracting to contracting for Credit Unions, to build a client base within my target audience for <a href="http://www.pennyminder.com/">Pennyminder</a> (which is (finally!) starting to gain some traction). And since Pennyminder already has a blurb about development services, it seemed redundant to have it in two places.</p>

<p>That being said, I am always interested in hearing about interesting projects, so feel free to give me a shout!</p>

<h2>Technical blog</h2>

<p>I will admit something up front, I am a horrible and infrequent blogger.  But...there are things that I want to talk about and this will be the blog with the technical articles in it (where as the pennyminder blog will be less technical).</p>

<h2>Things I am working on and/or want to write about</h2>

<ul>
<li>Guard Planning, a new SaaS app that aims to take the pain away for security companies' management of staff and schedules.  Somet hings to talk about with project.</li>
<li>"Spending Habits" and "Bill Reminders",  new features for <a href="http://www.pennyminder.com/cashbook.html">Pennyminder Cashbook</a>.  These will also be available as stand alone modules that can be implemented independant of Cashbook.  (I am also considering offering a consumer facing version of the service)</li>
<li>Updatebroker, a little service for delivering updates to channels when things happen asynchronously (great for multiuser apps!)</li>
<li>Crumbs, an ultra minimal stream of thought journaling tool. More to come!</li>
<li>Realtime push updates from modern RDBMS's, to help show CU and the world that real time need not be all that hard.</li>
<li>And of course sales and marketing for Pennyminder (which I am not very good at it seems).</li>
</ul>


<h2>Site code and Design Inspiration</h2>

<p>While I feel the design is my own, it does borrow heavily from <a href="http://shashankmehta.in/archive/2012/greyshade.html">Greyshade by Shashank Mehta</a>.  It's nice and clean base to start from! It's powered by <a href="http://www.octopress.org/">Octopress</a> and hosted by <a href="http://pages.github.com/">Github Pages</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
